<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DistortEdgeEffect</string>
    <string name="long_text">Whenever an app runs in the background, it consumes some of the device\'s limited resources, like RAM. This can result in an impaired user experience, especially if the user is using a resource-intensive app, such as playing a game or watching video. To improve the user experience, Android 8.0 (API level 26) imposes limitations on what apps can do while running in the background. This document describes the changes to the operating system, and how you can update your app to work well under the new limitations Many Android apps and services can be running simultaneously. For example, a user could be playing a game in one window while browsing the web in another window, and using a third app to play music. The more apps are running at once, the more load is placed on the system. If additional apps or services are running in the background, this places additional loads on the system, which could result in a poor user experience; for example, the music app might be suddenly shut down.To lower the chance of these problems, Android 8.0 places limitations on what apps can do while users aren\'t directly interacting with them. Apps are restricted in two ways:Background Service Limitations: While an app is idle, there are limits to its use of background services. This does not apply to foreground services, which are more noticeable to the user.Broadcast Limitations: With limited exceptions, apps cannot use their manifest to register for implicit broadcasts. They can still register for these broadcasts at runtime, and they can use the manifest to register for explicit broadcasts targeted specifically at their app.\n In most cases, apps can work around these limitations by using JobScheduler jobs. This approach lets an app arrange to perform work when the app isn\'t actively running, but still gives the system the leeway to schedule these jobs in a way that doesn\'t affect the user experience. Android 8.0 offers several improvements to JobScheduler that make it easier to replace services and broadcast receivers with scheduled jobs; for more information, see JobScheduler improvements.</string>
</resources>